{
    "id": "9dbca10003d740db9a1ed127a1cb1b2b",
    "title": "Match the following",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "9f837996f57742db8fe4f13ba6af4b75",
            "title": "Fill In the Blanks",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "James .................................. at the party.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "enjoyed himself",
                        "enjoyed",
                        "enjoyed himselves"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is going to be more difficult .................................. we thought.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "than",
                        "then"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is not always obstinate, but .................................. she is.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "sometimes",
                        "some time",
                        "some times"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".................................... of money has been wasted on the project.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "A lot",
                        "Lot",
                        "Lots"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "How about ......................................... to the theater tonight?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go",
                        "we go",
                        "going"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was careless .............................. him to leave the keys of the safe on the table.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "for",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How clever ..................................... you to solve the problem so quickly.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "of",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The more he reads ...................................... he understands.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "the less",
                        "the lesser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The older we grow ........................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "we become the wiser",
                        "we become wiser",
                        "the wiser we become"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is very good ................................... languages.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with learning",
                        "at learning",
                        "at learn"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is interested ................................. the supernatural.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "in",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I must get my watch ..................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "repair",
                        "repaired",
                        "repairing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}